嘿，我的生活......
Hey, my life's...
每天每分钟...
every day...every minute...
不只是但凿自己每一刻！
not just that but every moment of it is chiselled by myself!
走得更快！
Walk faster!
去......你在这里，对不对？ 去......
Go...you're here, right? Go...
快趴下......
Get down quickly...
在队列中，你站在这一边。
In the queue, you stand this side.
加入就行了！ 站在线！ 我该死的命运！
Join the line! Stand in line! My damn fate!
我什么时候会得到配给卡？
When will I get ration card?
你听我的，而我说的是其他的人，对不对？
You heard me while I was telling the other man, right?
我再告诉你吗？
Do I've to tell you again?
一遍又一遍问同样的查询，你为什么拿我的命吗？
Why do you take my life asking the same query again and again?
滚开！
Go away!
下一个！
Next!
如果有其他地方打架，你来这里！
If there's a fight elsewhere, you come running here!
要夺走我们的生命！
To take our lives!
怎样的生活！
What a life!
叫什么名字？
Name?
比拉。 大卫・比拉。
Billa. David Billa.
你叫什么作为？ - 这取决于呼叫者。
What are you called as? - It depends on the caller.
你来自哪里？ - 从海！
Where are you coming from? - From sea!
我们知道！ 先生问你来自哪个地方？
We know that! Sir is asking which place are you coming from?
正确回答他。
Answer him properly.
地方吗？ - Pavalathurai。
Place? - Pavalathurai.
父亲？
Father?
妈妈？
Mother?
你是孤儿吗？
Are you an orphan?
没有！ 我的姐姐。
No! I've an elder sister.
她在哪儿？ - 在马德拉斯。
Where is she? - In Madras.
告诉我地址??。
Tell me the address.
我不知道。
I don't know.
到底什么你在干什么在Pavalathurai？
What the heck were you doing in Pavalathurai?
我是...
I was f...
检查他！
Check him!
你是恐怖分子？
Are you a terrorist?
有恐怖分子和叛乱分子之间只有一个区别，
There's just one difference between terrorist and insurgent,
胜利！...
...victory!
他是恐怖分子，直到他赢了。
He's terrorist till he wins.
有一次，他赢了，他是一个叛乱。
Once he wins, he's an insurgent.
他是否有任何标记？ - 不，先生。
Does he have any mark? - No sir.
什么？ - 纪念先生。
What? - No mark sir.
采取并让他拍摄。
Take and get him photographed.
你来吧。
Come.
来...来...
Come...come...
下一个！
Next!
防空洞在哪里？ - 我会告诉来。
Where's the shelter? - I'll show, come.
在饥饿的孩子哭，
Child is crying in hunger,
没有供应牛奶吗？ 当你提供？
didn't supply milk yet? When will you supply?
如果孩子不能喝牛奶几天会发生什么？
What would happen if the child doesn't drink milk for couple of days?
它会喝牛奶长大成为收藏家？
Will it grow up drinking milk to become a Collector?
什么？
What?
这是庇护所！
This is the shelter!
去！
Go!
新到货？ - 是的。
New arrival? - Yes.
叫什么名字？ - 比拉。
Name? - Billa.
你想另一个热，MUTHU的？
You want another one hot, Muthu?
取笑我吗？
Making fun of me?
Raghubir先生不知道你背叛了他，
Raghubir sir doesn't know you betrayed him,
这就是为什么你还活着，
that's why you're still alive,
如果他来了就知道了，你死定了。
if he comes to know, you'd be dead.
这些威胁，你不能吓唬我。
You can't scare me with these threats.
来吧，只要你喜欢说话！
Come on speak as you like!
去的人！ - 我带你去任务。
Go man! - I'll take you to task.
看，怎么MUTHU乱窜上看到你！
Look, how Muthu is scurrying on seeing you!
来吧兄弟！
Come brother!
4茶请！
4 teas please!
我们没有任何选择，所以我们呆在这里，
We don't have any choice so we've to stay here,
你说你一个妹妹，为什么不去找她？
you say you've a sister, why not go to her?
我的家人从来没有正确地理解我，
My family never understood me properly,
我怀疑，他们仍然不会。
I doubt still they will not.
不过，我一定会去给他们。
But I'll definitely go to them.
特种茶，弟弟。
Special tea, brother.
你看到的尊重你耳光MUTHU后？
Did you see the respect after you slapped Muthu?
给我的火炬。 - 以先生。
Give me the torch. - Take it sir.
这是混蛋吗？ - 不是他先生。
Is this bastard? - Not him sir.
这是混蛋吗？ - 先生，他是盲目的。
Is it this bastard? - Sir, he's blind.
他在哪里？ - 他在这里，先生。
Where is he? - He'd be somewhere here only, sir.
主席先生，让我们在这里检查。
Sir, let's check here.
在哪里？ 嘿，你！ 起床的人！
Where? Hey you! Get up man!
血腥！ 是他吗？ - 这是不是他，先生。
Bloody! Is it him? - It's not him, sir.
在哪里？ 他在哪里？
Where? Where is he?
嘿，你！ 起床！
Hey you! Get up!
是他吗？ - 先生，他们是新的阵营。
Is it him? - No sir, they're new to the camp.
他是谁？ 他在哪里？
Who is he? Where is he?
主席先生，他要去那里！
Sir, he's going there!
保持冷静！
Stay calm!
什么？ 你会做什么的人吗？
What? What will you do man?
血腥！
Bloody!
该死的混蛋！ 你只是一个毒品小贩，卖我的股票。
Bloody bastard! You're just a drug peddler selling my stock.
你会突然改革和背叛我？
Will you suddenly reform and betray me?
如果有人胆敢背叛我，这将是他的命运！
If anyone dares to betray me, this will be his fate!
嘿，MUTHU！ 把他关进大海！
Hey Muthu! Throw him into sea!
辛哈Raghubir！ 这个营地的安全管理人员。
Raghubir Sinha! Security officer of this camp.
如果任何人违背他是这样的结果。
If anyone goes against him this is the result.
它似乎Nilavan工程需要几个工人所在的工厂，
It seems the factory where Nilavan works need few more workers,
它似乎有一个星期的工作...
it seems there's work for a week...
嘿，你！ 过来！ - 我？
Hey you! Come here! - Me?
是的，你！ 过来！
Yes, you! Come here!
自行车，我们去车站。
Get on bike, we've to go to station.
爵士为什么？ 有什么问题吗？
Why sir? What's the matter?
一个被告已逃离，留在监狱里的一对夫妇的天。
An accused has escaped, stay in jail for a couple of days.
我会得到你为它付出。 - 不，先生，我去上班。
I'll get you paid for it. - No sir, I've to go to work.
我没有问，如果你来不来，我说我的自行车。
I didn't ask if you're coming or not, I said get on my bike.
不，先生，我不...
No sir, I'll not...
什么样的男人？ - 不，先生。
What man? - No sir.
你想死吗？ 鲜血淋漓......
You want to die? Bloody...
我们是难民。 不是孤儿。
We are refugees. Not orphans.
没有大卫，请听我说。 离开他。
No David, please listen to me. Leave him.
这是我能做些什么，
This is what I can do,
如果你想要做更多的东西，我们将他释放。
if you want to do anything more, we'll release him.
你可以做任何事情，他在外面。
You can do anything with him outside.
你说你不是一个孤儿，对不对？
You said you're not an orphan, right?
有没有人来救你了吗？
Hasn't anyone come to save you?
还有很多更多的等待！
There's much more pending!
我们需要5个工人，作画。
We need 5 workers to paint.
我告诉你，他们将采取每日工资的工人。
I told you they would take workers on daily wages.
嘿，你的蓝色背心，来了！
Hey you blue vest, come!
白色背心，你也一样！
White vest, you too!
嘿，你的蓝色头巾，来到这里。
Hey you blue lungi, come here.
我们需要木工作业的3人。
We need 3 people for carpentry job.
你来了......你......你走吧！
You come...you...you go!
我们需要3个金属制造。
We need 3 metalworkers.
你高大的人，来了。
You tall man, come.
嘿绿色隆吉，来了。
Hey green lungi, come.
嘿，大肚子，来了。
Hey potbelly, come.
这一切，如果我需要更多的工人，今天我会叫的！
That's all for today, if I need more workers, I'll call!
现在清除！ 去......去......去老太太！ 清除了！
Clear off now! Go...go...go lady! Clear off!
只要你得到你的工资必须得到我们的佣金。
Must get our commission as soon as you get your wages.
如果没有，我会成为不人道！ 你知道吗，对吧？
If not I'll become inhuman! You know it, right?
去吧，车辆停在那里，去！ 快！
Go, the vehicle is parked there, go! Quick!
哥...哥哥...
Brother...brother...
我有两个好工作你，为什么你要离开，哥哥？
I've got two good jobs for you, why are you going away, brother?
你会做吗？
Will you do it?
我们会，如果你付出。 - 争取然后准备好，我带你去。
We'll if you pay well. - Be ready then, I'll take you.
问候BHAI！
Greetings bhai!
来MUTHU！
Come Muthu!
问候BHAI！ - 发生了什么事？
Greetings bhai! - What happened?
你为什么迟到？
Why are you late?
巴伊，我告诉你两个人，对不对？
Bhai, I told you about two people, right?
的问候。
Greetings.
告诉我，先生。
Tell me sir.
我答应提供鱼党在马德拉斯，
I'd promised to supply fish to a party in Madras,
闪存罢工货车的人都走了，
lorry people have gone on a flash strike,
我很困惑，商品将衰减。
I'm confused, goods will decay.
如果将货物交付，我会保持我的诺言。
If you deliver the goods, I'd have kept my promise.
好吧。 你付出多少？
Okay. How much will you pay us?
通常情况下，我们支付3000卢比，在罢工期间我们支付Rs.3500。
Normally we pay Rs.3000, during strike we pay Rs.3500.
Rs.5000！
Rs.5000!
你的男人要求更多！
Your men are asking for more!
如果鱼腐烂，你把它扔回来入海，对不对？
If fish decay, you'd throw it back into sea, right?
还好BHAI，我们可以弥补在未来的行程。
Say okay bhai, we can compensate in next trip.
你带来了他们的承诺。
You brought them as promised.
我已经安排好了一切途中！
I've arranged everything enroute!
如果货物交付，我们将获得的利润，
If goods are delivered, we'll get profit,
如果它不交付的利润将是双重的。
if it's not delivered the profit will be double.
巴伊，以后，我会打电话给你走了。 - 好吧，先生。
Bhai, I'll call later, you go now. - Okay sir.
大卫，你应该已经给了2紧掴MUTHU的。
David, you should've given two more tight slaps to Muthu.
为什么呢？
Why?
我们得到了一巴掌Rs.5000！
We got Rs.5000 for one slap!
如果你打了他一巴掌，我们每个人的两倍就已经得到了Rs.5000，对不对？
Had you slapped him twice each one of us would've got Rs.5000, right?
吓坏了的鱼腐烂。
Got scared of fish decaying.
其他人的恐惧是我们的力量！
Others' fear is our strength!
后交付，让我们快乐地度过一个星期，马德拉斯和回来。
After delivering this, let's spend a week happily in Madras and come back.
我也满足了我的妹妹。
I'll also meet my sister.
拉过这一侧！
Pull over this side!
关闭你趴下。
Switch off and both of you get down.
你背着什么？
What are you carrying?
你冷吗，先生？ - 取笑我？
Do you've cold, sir? - Making fun of me?
不，臭味是如此的可怕。 你不能猜测它的鱼吗？
No, the stink is so terrible. Can't you guess its fish?
检查车辆。
Check the vehicle.
主席先生，钻石！
Sir, diamonds!
发生了什么事，潘店？ - 他们抓住了，先生。
What happened, Pandian? - They're caught, sir.
把货物给我。 - 好吧，先生。
Bring the goods to me. - Okay, sir.
如果一条鱼有这么多的钻石，其他鱼有多少？
If one fish has so many diamonds, how many would other fish have?
如果我们把它剪断，我们发财了！
If we cut it, we could make a fortune!
让出售其关闭，并在生活中安顿下来。
Let's sell it off and settle down in life.
你说什么？
What do you say?
让我们交付货物。
Let's deliver the goods.
站起身来这么早，Annachi？
Got up so early, Annachi?
问候兄弟。
Greetings brother.
是兄弟。
Yes brother.
从鲜奶咖啡。 - 好兄弟。
Get coffee from fresh milk. - Okay brother.
看起来就像你开的店吗？
Looks like you've opened the shop?
我还能做什么呢？ 我开网店，不惜任何代价。
What else can I do? I've to open shop at any cost.
这是我们的专业。 - 你说得对。
That's our profession. - You're right.
嘿DOSA高手！ - 什么是什么，先生？
Hey dosa master! - What's it, sir?
不要添加盐的面糊，我已经加入了它。
Don't add salt to the batter, I've already added it.
好的，先生。
Okay sir.
然后......
Then...
我觉得茄子负荷已经到来，我可以给你打电话？
I think brinjal load has come, can I call you later?
我记得，Annachi。 稍后我会打电话给你。
I remember it, Annachi. I'll call you later.
好吧，不要忘记它。
Okay, don't forget it.
Rameshwaram。 - 我欢迎你的传统。
No, Rameshwaram. - I welcomed you traditionally.
你必须说湿婆奇丹巴拉姆。
You must say Siva Chidambaram.
我应该说是湿婆奇丹巴拉姆？ 然后Selvaraj ...
Should I say Siva Chidambaram? Then Selvaraj...
人们都叫我喜欢。 你想点什么？
People call me like that. What would you like to have?
茉莉花袖手旁观，的白paniyaram！ 多萨！ Poori和土豆泥。
Jasmine idly, white paniyaram! Dosa! Poori and potato mash.
带来的鱼... 到错误的地址。 再见！
Brought fish... to the wrong address. Bye!
哥，回来了。 你来吧。
Brother, come back. Come.
你已经来到了正确的地方，你是BHAI的人，对不对？ - 是。
You've come to the right place, you're bhai's man, right?- Yes.
把卡车后院，我会加入你。
Bring the truck to backyard, I'll join you there.
你的意思是......？ - 我的意思是背面！
You mean...? - I mean back side!
保持在那里。 洗手来早餐。
Keep it there. Wash your hands and come for breakfast.
我们已经被骗了，塞尔瓦！ 我发送的货物不见了！
We've been cheated, Selva! Goods I've sent is gone!
我没有得到你！
I don't get you!
我相信新的男性和发送货物。
I trusted new men and sent the goods.
他们已经消失了的商品。
They've vanished with the goods.
如果我找回来，我会杀了他们！
If I find them again, I'll slaughter them!
谁，你会的屠宰，BHAI？
Who will you slaughter, bhai?
相信我，我不知道警察会检查货车。
Trust me, I didn't know police would check the lorry.
相信我，大卫。
Trust me, David.
兄弟，告诉他。
Brother, tell him.
离开它，BHAI。
Leave it, bhai.
警方检查后，油，它是所有孩子的东西，BHAI。 进来，BHAI。
Police, check-post, oil, it's all kid stuff, bhai. Come in, bhai.
如何Raghubir在做什么？
How is Raghubir doing?
看起来像你怀疑我。 相信我，塞尔瓦。
Looks like you're suspecting me. Trust me, Selva.
请进来。
Please come in.
多少生意，我们就已经完成，并获得利润呢？
How much business we would've done and earned profit?
我会做什么错？ - 请槟榔叶。
Would I do anything wrong? - Please have betel leaves.
告诉我。 - 咀嚼槟榔叶，BHAI的。
Tell me. - Chew betel leaves, bhai.
咀嚼它。 咀嚼它，我说，B??HAI！
Chew it. Chew it I say, bhai!
死蜥蜴躺在里面，清除它关闭。
A dead lizard is lying inside, clear it off.
你要留在哪里？
Where are you going to stay?
为了缓解bodyaches得到很好的按摩了两天，
To relieve bodyaches, get good massage for two days,
我们要振兴后我们回家。
we want to go back home after rejuvenating us.
就拿它。
Take it.
我们已经支付的工作。
We've been paid for the job.
这是你想要做什么，这是为将来的工作。
That's for what you'd done, this is for future job.
我是一个女孩从马杜赖...
I'm a girl from Madurai...
敢把我在你的怀里...
Dare take me in your arms...
我是一朵奇葩...
I'm exotic flower...
不敢惹咬我......
Dare touch and bite me...
我的一半纱丽跟着我...
My half sari follows me...
我的愿望在我之前...
My desire precedes me...
天使是在这里为你...
Angel is here for you...
这是一个值得庆祝的年龄...
It's an age to celebrate...
看着我的眼睛是雪亮的激光...
Watching my laser sharp eyes...
很多城镇跟着我...
Many a towns followed me...
我的心被宠坏了，因为你...
My heart is spoiled because of you...
不稳定的青年...
Unstable youth...
董事会战车的幸福...
Board the chariot of happiness...
如果你有任何疑问，来，抱抱我......
If you've any doubt, come and hug me...
我的身体是云，翱翔天空高成...
My body is cloud, soar high into sky...
变成雨降下来...
Come down turning into rain...
你的爱在这里是无效的......
Your love is not valid here...
但你的钱是有效的，在这里...
But your money is valid here...
这个地方是战场灯谜......
This place is battlefield of riddles...
失败是胜利在这里...
Defeat is also victory here...
所有人都是平等的，这是一个床......
It's a bed where all are equal...
一个更多请！
One more please!
要小心的男孩！
Be careful boys!
不要洗掉泥钻石！
Don't wash off diamonds along with mud!
父亲？ 妈妈？
Father? Mother?
你是孤儿吗？
Are you an orphan?
叔叔！
Uncle!
它已经多年，因为我看到你了！
It's been years since I saw you!
你怎么样，大卫？ - 我没事。
How are you doing, David? - I'm fine.
你什么时候来？ - 前几天。
When did you come? - Few days ago.
你好
How do you do?
怎么回事。
Going on.
至少现在，你想满足你的妹妹。
At least now you thought of meeting your sister.
我很高兴，
I'm happy-
你怎么样，茉莉？ - 精细。 你给我带来了什么？
How are you, Jasmine? - Fine. What have you brought for me?
你会不会保持沉默？
Won't you keep quiet?
你问他总是有东西吗？
Will you ask him something always?
如果我问什么是错的？ 我有一种权利，不是吗？
What's wrong if I ask? I do have a right, don't I?
她问我，对不对？ 离开妹妹。
She's asking me, right? Leave it sister.
您所输入的枪的人来与圣经。
You've entered with gun where people come with Bible.
无论是你当时也没有现在的改革！
Neither you reformed then nor now!
你永远不会改革。
You'll never reform.
叔叔已经很长一段时间后。 你担心他。
Uncle has come after long time. You were worried about him.
为什么你现在喊他吗？
Why are you shouting on him now?
闭嘴！ 你来吧。
Shut up! Come.
叔叔，你知道妈妈，请不要把它严重。
Uncle, you know about mother, please don't take it serious.
保持它的费用。 - 不用了。
Keep it for expenses. - No need.
经常访问我们，这就足够了。
Visit us often, that's enough.
大哥！
Brother!
你为什么要在煮沸的牛奶？ 去！
Why have you over boiled the milk? Go!
的问候！
Greetings!
你为什么来，晚上穿着大衣呢？
Why have you come at night wearing a coat?
我在这里工作。 - 好吧坐在这里。
I'm here on a job. - Okay sit here.
坐在这里，一切都是我的孩子们。
Sit here, all are my boys.
他是大卫，这是兰吉特。 这是拉姆！
He's David, that's Ranjit. That's Ram!
大卫，他KOTI！ 我的老朋友从果阿。
David, he's Koti! My old friend from Goa.
是你的老板阿巴西罚款？
Is your boss Abbasi fine?
他究竟缺少什么呢？ 他很高兴。
What does he lack? He's happy.
但是我... - 什么是你错了吗？
But I'm... - What's wrong with you?
我说什么？ 带来了卢比亿卢比值得粉剂。
What am I to tell? Brought Rs.1 crore worth powder.
党在最后时刻消失。
Party vanished in the last moment.
我很茫然。 - 是的材料安全吗？
I'm all at sea. - Is the material safe?
回到它带回家。
Go back to home with it.
无兄弟，很难再带回来。
No brother, very difficult to take it back.
我想，把它推到有人在这里只。
I want to push it off to someone here only.
如果你能帮我... - 哦，不！ 毒品是我忌讳。
If you help me... - Oh no! Drugs are taboo to me.
我会做到这一点。
I'll do it.
你知不知道这个决定会带你吗？
Do you know where this decision will take you?
时代已经改变了。
Times have changed.
它的机灵与时并进，改变业务。
It's smartness to change business with times.
如果没有，我们将被甩在后面。
If not we would be left behind.
KOTI，大卫是非常渴望的，给他的细节。
Koti, David is very eager, give him the details.
就拿它。
Take it.
快来明天晚上10点到这个地址。
Come tomorrow at 10 pm to this address.
然后我会跟我的老板，再见Annachi。
By then I'll talk to my boss, bye Annachi.
大卫，你太勇敢了！
David, you're too brave!
我觉得你希望比你更可以处理。
I feel you're wishing for more than you can handle.
它不希望Annachi，它的饥饿感！
It's not wish, Annachi, it's hunger!
为什么这突如其来的变化，大卫？
Why this sudden change, David?
如果我们去那里的时间提前，
If we go there ahead of the time,
我们完全信任他，他会带我们容易思维，
he would take us easy thinking we trust him fully,
如果我们迟到10分钟，他会带我们不负责任，
if we go 10 minutes late, he would take us as irresponsible,
但是，如果我们到达那里的时候，
but if we reach there on time,
他会得到希望，我们将完成这项工作。
he'll get hope that we would finish the job.
现在的时间是晚上10点！
Now the time is 10 pm!
欢迎大卫！
Welcome David!
你想点什么？
What would you like to have?
我们汩汩口苏格兰威士忌！
We gurgle mouth with Scotch!
我们能谈生意吗？
Can we talk business?
我跟我的老板。
I've talked to my boss.
这是海洛因！
This is heroin!
这是值得卢比亿卢比！
It's worth Rs.1 crore!
如果你卖掉它，我将付给你Rs.50000！
If you sell it, I'll pay you Rs.50000!
5％！
5%!
完成交易，并来到果阿！
Finish the deal and come to Goa!
把你的份额。
Take your share there.
告诉你的老板约5％的佣金是什么？
What about telling you boss about 5% commission?
他从来没有采取任何决定，没有跟我讨论。
He never takes any decision without discussing with me.
你将如何找到一个买家？
How would you find a buyer for this?
这是很难找到好男人！ 再见！
It's difficult only to find good men! Bye!
，确保RANJITH与RAM，Kadhir外，你跟我来。
Ranjith, you secure outside with Ram, Kadhir, you come with me.
兄弟在里面。
Brother is inside.
有！
There!
您已经砰的时间！
You've bang on time!
你的名字吗？
Your name?
你带的是什么？
What have you brought?
是吗？
Yes?
检查那个东西是什么！
Check what that thing is!
海洛因，兄弟。
Heroin, brother.
保持它里面。
Keep it inside.
你为什么还在这里？ 走了。
Why are you still here? Get going.
钱？
Money?
你怎么敢给我粉，并要求金钱！
How dare you give me the powder and ask money!
去的人！ 走出去全面！
Go man! Go out in full!
你这个愚蠢的吗？ 会有人给股票没有钱吗？
Are you foolish? Would anyone give stock without money?
Foofish？
Foofish?
你叫我愚蠢吗？
Did you call me foolish?
我会告诉你我的专长！
I'll show you my expertise!
男孩！ 请保持静止！
Boy! Please stay still!
我告诉你，出门全！ 你现在看到的吗？
I told you to go out in full! Did you see now?
他们在很长一段时间。 - 我会检查。
They're in for long time. - I'll check.
停止...停...
Stop...stop...
你问我的名字，对不对？ 比拉！ 大卫・比拉！
You asked my name, right? Billa! David Billa!
去！
Go!
KOTI你告诉我，你有没有满足KOTI？
Koti told me about you, did you meet Koti?
我见过你，对不对？
I've met you, right?
回到你的股票给你感到惊讶。
Surprised for returning your stock to you.
我给你的礼物！
MY gift to you!
让我们相约今天晚上。
Let's meet today evening.
中毒排序填补了空气...
A sort of intoxication fills up the air...
它会吸进去......
It'll suck you into it...
一旦进入你的心会下降...
Once entered your heart will fall for it...
这个世界是新的世界......
This world is new world...
的世界中，您可以看到，即使睁大眼睛...
A world you can't see even with eyes wide open...
你正在寻找的人...
The man you're searching...
你甜言蜜语的男人就在你面前...... 他热烈拥抱...
Your sweet man is right before you... hug him hotly...
你的眼睛看到的是弥天大谎......
What you see with eyes is blatant lie...
见的泪水，甚至是谎言成为真理...
See the tears, even lies would become truth...
你想要什么都寻求在这里...
What ever you want seek here...
就拿我的心啊，男孩...
Take on my heart, O boy...
如果有中毒在你的眼前，你可以赢得一天...
If there's intoxication in your eyes, you can win the day...
如果你赢了，世界跟着你......
If you win, the world follows you...
你的生活是破碎的生活... 团结起来吧......
Your life is broken life... unite it...
来吧，让我们一起看看新的世界......
Come, let's see the new world together...
你喜欢晚上，大卫？
Did you enjoy the evening, David?
你喜欢我的俱乐部吗？
Do you like my club?
你自己的天堂，问我，我是否喜欢它。
You own the heaven and asking me whether I like it.
有看得多，是我的客人观看。
There's much more to see, be my guest to watch it.
海岸卫队缴获Dimitri的武器运输。
Coastal Guards have seized Dimitri's arms consignment.
他寻求我的帮助。
He's seeking my help.
他准备支付卢比亿卢比。
He's ready to pay Rs.20 crores.
没有阿巴斯，我们没有任何人在该部门。
No Abbasi, we don't have anyone in that department.
预防武器的行为是非常艰难的。
Arms prevention act is very tough.
是的，没有必要进入最国际刑警组织通缉名单卢比亿卢比。
Yes, no need to get into most wanted Interpol list for Rs.20 crores.
现在的货物在哪里？
Where is the consignment now?
我们已经四舍五入的地方，先生。
We've rounded up the place, sir.
你在这里，我觉得我得到额外的能量。
With you here, I feel like I'm getting extra energy.
主席先生，我该交易完成后，你可能会忘记。
Sir, you may forget me after this deal is done.
让我看看！
Let me see!
你为什么在这里与未来的首席部长，KOTI？
Why are you here with future Chief Minister, Koti?
你打算参与政治吗？
Are you planning to join politics?
他想亲自和你谈谈。 所以，我把他交给你。
He wanted to talk to you personally. So I've brought him to you.
选举拐角处？ 您需要任何帮助。
Are elections round the corner? You need any help.
我们需要很多！
We need a lot!
我可以不赚钱，因为我觉得，直到有这个首席部长。
I can't make money as I think till this Chief Minister is there.
所以，如果我的儿子萨蒂什加入，他将学习贸易和使杀！
So if my son Satish joins you, he'll learn the trade and make a kill!
什么是坏主意？
What is bad idea?
他的加入我们吗？ - 不，我们加入他！
Does his joining us? - No, we joining him!
不要说没有理解它。
Don't talk without understanding it.
我们会得到政府的支持。
We'll get Government backing.
我的权力，你的勇气，我们可以排除的地方。
I've power, you've courage, we can rule the place.
动力和勇气，不但不能执行这项业务。
Power and courage only can't run this business.
你需要更多的资格。
You need more qualifications.
我在30年的政治，你说我不是合格的？
I'm in politics for 30 years, do you say I'm not qualified?
如果你犯了一个错误，你就会失去座位仅电力，
If you commit a mistake,you'll lose seat of power only,
但在这项业务中，我们失去了生命。
but in this business we lose life.
阿巴西，我不是在这里和他谈谈。
Abbasi, I'm not here to talk to him.
你侮辱了我。
You've insulted me.
要准备面对音乐。
Be ready to face the music.
告诉我，茉莉花
Tell me, Jasmine
愿我们的姐妹的灵魂安息。
May the soul of our sister rest in peace.
愿上帝保佑她的灵魂。
May God bless her soul.
愿她的灵魂安息！ 阿门！
May her soul rest in peace! Amen!
房子很漂亮。
House is very beautiful.
她Mrs.Pedro。
She's Mrs.Pedro.
她会做什么都想要。
She'll do what ever you want.
你会不会留在这儿呢？
Won't you stay here then?
你会在哪里停留？
Where will you stay?
在我的老板的宾馆。
In my boss' guest house.
必须满足阿巴西。 - 好吧。
Have to meet Abbasi. - Okay.
我还以为你和我呆在一起，叔叔，但你说没有。
I thought you'd stay with me, uncle but you say no.
我带来了申请加入学院，填补它。
I've brought application to join college, fill it up.
好吧。
Okay.
我们承诺的钱已经存入把寄售的安全。
They've deposited our promised money for bringing the consignment safely.
让这种危险的是与你的安全。
Let this danger be safe with you.
迪米特里希望您来参观Barovia荣誉的友谊。
Dimitri wants you to visit Barovia to honour the friendship.
KOTI会以我的名义。
Koti will come on my behalf.
大卫也将与你同在。
David will also come with you.
鲍比也与你同在。
Take Bobby also with you.
她知道的语言。
She knows the language.
迪米特里出现像一个很好的人，但很危险。
Dimitri appears like a good man but very dangerous.
要小心！
Be careful!
反正你会为了唯一的冰淇淋，对不对？
Anyway you'll order only ice cream, right?
我要Barovia的业务。
I'm going to Barovia on business.
它会采取... - 我也跟你一起去。
It'll take... - I'll also come with you.
请带我还用你说。 - 我说的业务。
Please take me also with you. - I said business.
你为什么不试着了解我??...
Why don't you try to understand me...
你能不能带我，如果它的业务？
Can't you take me if it's business?
8时，我会在那里！
I'll be there at 8!
你好
How do you do?
她是Sameera吗？ 我得到了它。
Is she Sameera? I got it.
他想先显示周围的工厂。
He wants to show around the factory first.
M4，一分钟可以发射900发子弹。
M4, can fire 900 bullets for a minute.
70万美元的生意，
70 million dollar business,
他的业务总价值300万。
his total business is worth 300 millions.
武器有这么大的市场吗？
Do arms have such a big market?
这不是一个市场的武器，但死亡！
It's not a market for arms, but for death!
直到死亡，手臂有市场。
Till there's death, arms will have a market.
他询问，如果你喜欢工厂。
He's asking if you like the factory.
我非常喜欢它，我希望把我们的业务到一个新的水平。
I like it very much, I want to take our business to next level.
迪米特里将设法达成一项协议，
Dimitri will try to seal a deal,
不咨询阿巴西没有作出任何决定。
don't take any decision without consulting Abbasi.
他已发送你陪我，不要忘记它。
He has sent you to accompany me, don't forget it.
你害怕吗？
Are you scared?
不要住在这里，当我们帮你搞定，保持。
Don't stay here when we seal the deal, keep out.
不，我不是故意这样的。
No, I didn't mean like that.
迪米特里给我们打电话。
Dimitri is calling us.
他承诺帮助我们做任何事情。
He's promising to do anything for our help.
我们想加入您的军火生意。
We want to join your arms business.
我听说过他。
I've heard about him.
他得到我的部门支付。 他也知道这一点。
He's getting paid by my department. He too knows it.
你也有，怎么会这样呢？
You too were there, how could this happen?
他不听我的话。
He didn't listen to me.
你有没有业务发展理念，KOTI？
Have you given any business development idea, Koti?
他的愤怒。
He's angry.
为什么我送你到Barovia？
Why did I send you to Barovia?
你做了什么吗？ 我怀疑你。
What have you done there? I suspect you.
这是您的怀疑或KOTI？
Is this your suspicion or Koti's?
看你的交易将让任何人怀疑你。
Watching your deals will make anyone suspect you.
阿巴西，我没有做任何事情悄悄。
Abbasi, I don't do anything stealthily.
你知道我很好。
You know very well about me.
我知道鲍比比你之前。
I know Bobby much before than you.
我最信任的副官，他现在已经死了。
I trusted lieutenant, he's dead now.
最信任的副官？ 鲍比？
Trusted lieutenant? Bobby?
鲍比是国际刑警组织的线人。
Bobby is an Interpol informer.
他是因为我很年轻的年龄。
He was with me since very young age.
我敢肯定，他不会背叛了我们。
I'm sure he wouldn't have betrayed us.
每一个谁背叛了至今唯一信任的副手。
Every one who had betrayed till now were trusted lieutenants only.
你去那里观光，谁允许达成交易？
You went there on sight seeing, who permitted to strike a deal?
我想采取业务到一个新的水平，并为你达成了一项协议。
I wanted to take business to next level and struck a deal for you.
你知道每年利润的军火走私？
Do you know the yearly profit of arms smuggling?
让它成为数十亿美元，但你是谁决定哪些业务应该阿巴西做？
Let it be billions but who are you to decide what business should Abbasi do?
我跟你说话，阿巴西。
I'm talking to you, Abbasi.
KOTI话有什么错？
What's wrong in Koti's words?
你怎么知道迪米特里？
What do you know about Dimitri?
与他的军火生意就像是自杀。
Arms business with him is like committing suicide.
相信我，阿巴西。
Trust me, Abbasi.
我们必须面对的任何问题，因为这个。
We mustn't face any problem because of this.
谨慎行事！
Tread carefully!
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
你想要什么？
What do you want?
什么？
What?
大卫，请留在我身边......
David, Please stay with me...
你要走了吗？ 去！
Are you leaving? Go!
我知道你要去哪里！
I know where you are going!
我的错误是什么？
What was my mistake?
我只希望与你同在。
I wished to be with you only.
我不喜欢这招你惹你。
I did like this to provoke you.
阿巴西，让大卫在检查。
Abbasi, keep David under check.
我们的部门正面临着很多问题，因为他
Our department is facing lot of problems because of him
他曾殴打起来部长PRAVEEN的儿子在公共场所。
He has beaten up Minister Praveen's son in a public place.
如果他进一步做任何事情，我不得不对他采取行动，
If he does anything further and I'm forced to take action on him,
你最终可能会陷入困境。
you may end up in trouble.
我以后不要后悔。
Don't regret on me later.
我告诉你，但你不听从我。
I told you but you didn't heed me.
他在这里，直接问他。
He's here, ask him directly.
什么是您的投诉，这个时候，KOTI？
What's your complaint this time, Koti?
对于行动人谁用我敬礼，
For you action a man who used to salute me,
坐在前警告我。
is sitting right before and warning me.
我做了什么？ - 你为什么打Sathish所在？
What have I done? - Why did you beat Sathish?
如果有人行为不端的茉莉花，我会击败他们。
If anyone misbehaves with Jasmine, I'll beat them.
茉莉花是谁？
Who is Jasmine?
这是我个人的。
That's my personal.
它是个人的吗？ 已经生气PRAVEEN我们。
Is it personal? Already Praveen is angry on us.
现在，他已经击败了他的儿子。
Now he has beaten up his son.
你知不知道有多少，这会影响我的业务？
Do you know how much this would affect my business?
我的生意？ 我觉得你是别有用心。
My business? I think you've an ulterior motive.
直出来。
Come out straight.
从一个心腹，我不需要隐瞒什么。
I don't need to hide anything from a henchman.
我是你的朋友，当我安全带来迪米特里的手臂委托，
I was your friend when I safely brought Dimitri's arm consignment,
你看我像你的心腹吗？
do I look like an henchman to you now?
大卫，你过你的极限天天！
David, you're crossing your limits day by day!
看阿巴西！ 你已经决定的东西。
Look Abbasi! You've decided on something.
我会给我的生活的朋友。
I'll give my life for friend.
如果变成一个敌人，你会取他的性命呢？
If one becomes an enemy, will you take his life?
如果有必要大卫将做到这一点。
If it is necessary David will do it.
有没有大卫没有阿巴西。
There's no David without Abbasi.
有一个人冒着生命危险工作的区别，
There's difference between a man who risks his life to work,
和谁坐在舒适的家中工作。
and one who works sitting in the comforts of home.
记住！
Remember that!
我已经决定了！
I've decided!
我们要我们自己这样做毒品生意。
We're going to do this drug business on our own.
切勿情绪作出任何决定。
Never take any decision emotionally.
这将永远是错误的。
It will always be wrong.
我们已经采取了正确的决定。
We've taken the right decision now.
我们已经为他做了这么多钱。
We've made so much money for him.
还等什么？ 他在这个行业多年。
So what? He's in this business for years.
他让你成长？
Would he let you grow?
他不会。 - 然后呢？
He will not. - Then?
我们还必须让他去做。
We must also not let him do it.
好吧，你的计划是什么？
Okay, what's your plan?
我们在嘉年华当天密封俄罗斯交易。
We're sealing the Russian deal on carnival day.
你想要去加拿大，这是它。
You wanted to go to Canada, this is for it.
这是为了接受做我的工作。
This is for accepting to do my job.
接受和完成。
For accepting and accomplishing it.
什么是保证你会不会背叛我，像你这样的与大卫？
What's the guaranty that you'll not betray me like you did with David?
我告诉你之前，
I told you before,
有风险工作生活之间的差异，
there's difference between one who risks life to work,
和谁坐在舒适的家中工作。
and one who sits in the comforts of home to work.
为什么你误判大卫・比拉？
Why did you misjudge David Billa?
我应该已经采取了你个人，这是我的错误，信任他人。
I should've taken you personally, it's my mistake to trust others.
我不会请求你的宽恕，杀了我吧！
I'll not ask your forgiveness, kill me!
杀了我！
Kill me!
大卫，他威胁要杀死我，这就是为什么...
David, he threatened to kill me, that's why...
人们可以杀死成千上万的敌人，赢得
One can kill thousands of enemies to win,
这是没有错的，
it's not wrong,
但它是一个严重的错误，甚至腾出一个背叛者！
but it's a grave mistake to spare even one betrayer!
你内心的野兽...
Beast inside you...
试图休息...
Tries to rest...
如果它醒来，走...
If it wakes up and walks...
火山将爆发...
Volcanoes will erupt...
它作为食物会问你的梦想...
It'll ask your dreams as food...
它会吃掉你，并在你的手...
It'll devour you and be in your hand...
你不能得到蜂蜜不燃烧......
You can't get honey without burning it...
球会不会提高，除非你踢它......
The ball will not raise unless you kick it...
适者生存...
The fittest will survive...
这是法治的性质...
That's the rule of the nature...
如果你生活在地狱里，你必须成为一个野兽......
If you live in hell, you must become a beast...
牺牲和吓唬人... 提高一次又一次的黑客...
Sacrifice and scare people... raise again and again on hacking...
世界是不是圆的......
World is not round...
在这个世界上没有表单影子...
There's no form to shadow in this world...
打破规则，使自己的规则...
Break the rules and make your own rules...
有没有朋友在这里，这里没有敌人...
There's no friend here and no enemy here...
你是你唯一的朋友和你的敌人......
You're your only friend and your enemy too...
第一拳必须使敌人哆嗦，...
First punch must make enemy shiver...
下一页冲必须奴役他......
Next punch must enslave him...
如果他再次起身再次击中了他，这个时候敲他的生活......
If he gets up again hit him again, this time knock-out his life...
你死了，每天和每天重生...
You die every day and be born again every day...
警惕甚至睡觉时睁大眼睛......
Be alert even while asleep with eyes wide open...
你是你的问题，你是你的边界......
You're your problem and you're your boundary...
你的触摸撕刺，...
Your touch will tear the thorn...
虽然这是痛苦的，没有痛苦......
Though it's painful, there's no pain...
适者生存...
The fittest will survive...
这是法治的性质...
That's the rule of the nature...
不要杀我先生。
Don't kill me sir.
托运不会没有我寸步难行。
Your consignment will not move an inch without me.
主席先生！
Sir!
主席先生，你的支票！
Sir, your cheque!
官立。 不只是不足以消除贫困计划和金钱。
Govt. plans and money aren't just enough to eradicate poverty.
大卫・比拉国家福利基金，捐赠卢比亿卢比
David Billa has donated Rs.1 crore to state welfare fund,
我们会花这个钱的人唯一的福利。
we'll spend the money for the welfare of people only.
我希望这里的客人会很慷慨地捐赠资金的状态。
I hope guests here would generously donate funds to the state.
我很高兴，你做了它。
I'm happy that you made it.
卢比亿卢比...国家福利基金。
Rs.1 crore...state welfare fund.
这是公众。
That's for public.
但是因为有了你什么都想要多少都想要。
But for you what ever you want or how much ever you want.
任何时间！
Any time!
我准备放弃。
I'm ready to give.
如果你靠勤奋，成长到这个位置
Had you grown to this position by hard work,
你就不会这样说话，
you wouldn't speak like this,
你是一个强盗，并上升到这个位置的捷径。
you were a gangster and rose to this position in short cut.
无论你是商人或苦力还是乞丐，
Whether one is business man or a coolie or a beggar,
每个人都有辛劳，
everyone has to toil,
你是首席部长，
you're a Chief Minister,
你劳碌得来的国家和人民的福利，
you toil for the welfare of the state and its people,
你需要帮助的歹徒像我这样拿上你的敌人。
you need help of gangsters like me to take on your enemies.
你误会了我。
You've mistaken me.
此CM是不卖！
This CM is not for sale!
智能翼给您的完整信息。
Intelligence wing is giving complete information about you.
来吧，让我们下去。
Come, let's go down.
你走了，我会一直追随。
You go, I'll follow.
请留下我一个人。
Please leave me alone.
为什么呢？ CM说什么？
Why? What did the CM say?
我向你保证，这种情况下，我们会彻底调查，
I assure you this case will be thoroughly investigated,
犯罪分子将得到惩罚。
and the criminals will get punished.
在党的机构会议将选举产生新的CM。
New CM will be elected in the party's general body meeting.
我希望人们不要让情绪激动，在这些测试时间维持和平。
I want people not to get agitated and maintain peace in these testing times.
部长，没有人能配合你的动作。
Minister, nobody can match your moves.
你在说什么？
What are you saying?
迪米特里想比拉死。
Dimitri wants Billa dead.
你想成为CM和目前CM必须死定了。
You want to become CM and present CM must be dead.
你已经完成了所有三个。
You've accomplished all three.
此后，我们迪米特里在印度的贸易伙伴。
Hereafter we're Dimitri's business partners in India.
不庆祝，比拉是还没有死。
Don't celebrate, Billa is not yet dead.
他在监狱里。
He's in jail.
他不能出来。
He can't come out.
他寻求保释。
He has sought bail.
还等什么？ 我见过他威胁CM。
So what? I've seen him threatening CM.
有很多目击证人。
There are many eye witnesses.
此外，我们所生产的证据是很强的。
Moreover evidence produced by us is very strong.
他怎么来了？
How can he come out?
如果他仍然设法保释出来，
If he still manages to come out on bail,
有没有采取货币形式意义。
there's no meaning for taking money form you.
大卫・比拉是谁站在这里，作为被告，
David Billa who is standing here as the accused,
事发当天，他喝醉了酒，
on the day of the incident, he was drunk,
威胁CM，以帮助他在他的生意。
and was threatening CM to help him in his business.
有许多在场的人亲眼目睹了这
Many people present there witnessed this,
事实上，有媒体渠道，它与视频片段。
in fact there's video footage of it with media channels.
如果你让他保释出来，
If you let him out on bail,
他可以消灭我们的证据，并威胁证人。
he can wipe our evidence and threaten witnesses.
他理应受到严厉惩罚，你的荣誉。
He deserves to be punished severely, your honour.
因此，我要求法院不给予保释比拉。
So I request this court not to grant bail to Billa.
眼看你的情感倾诉与CM在功能，
Seeing your emotional talk with the CM in the function,
Praveen库马尔起到了肮脏的游戏。
Praveen Kumar played a dirty game.
我想我也不会获得保释，你是怎么管理的？
I thought I wouldn't get bail, how did you manage it?
你告诉我，别人的恐惧是我们的强项。
You told me that others' fear is our strength.
我把它应用。
I applied it.
你知道，我已经很长一段时间以来的第三部份，
You know I've a third majority since long time,
我不能让大家部长，对不对？
I can't make everyone a Minister, right?
让我先成为CM！
Let me become CM first!
之后我会受到质疑！
After there I'll be unchallenged!
难道你不相信我吗？
Don't you trust me?
我为这一天等待多年。
I was waiting years for this day.
我有...
I have...
希望成为CM和孵化的计划，
Desiring to become CM and hatching a plan for it,
它的所有政治，
it's all politics,
但它送我去监狱是愚昧。
but sending me to jail for it is foolishness.
你会杀了我吗？
Will you kill me now?
有没有资格成为我的朋友。
There's no qualification to become my friend.
但需要资格成为我的敌人。
But one needs qualification to become my enemy.
你没有任何。
You don't have any.
我决定，我会杀了你从监狱...
Had I decided I would've killed you from jail...
不要说像一个傻瓜，如果有什么发生在我身上，
Don't talk like a fool, if anything happens to me,
有万卢比的人，我给他们的生活。
there are lakhs of people to give their lives for me.
人们可能会为你投票，但不会放弃对你的生活。
People may vote for you but won't give life for you.
我就不班门弄斧到您的区域，
I'll not trespass into your area,
就不班门弄斧了我区！
don't trespass into my area!
告诉我，先生。
Tell me sir.
比拉来警告我。
Billa had come to warn me.
我要听到他的死讯。
I must hear his death news.
你怎么样？
How are you?
我回家了，对不对？ 你为什么要哭呢？
I'm home, right? Why are you crying?
我祈祷你早日获释。
I was praying for your early release.
有一个谈话，你会死在邂逅。
There's a talk that you'd be killed in an encounter.
迪米特里和比拉过一次交手。
Dimitri and Billa had a fight.
他希望在印度的合作伙伴。 如果你说是的，我会跟他谈。
He wants a partner in India. If you say yes, I'll talk to him.
你知道我是多么害怕吗？ 你在笑！
Do you know how scared I was? You're laughing!
你太害怕。
You're too scared.
我没想到你会这么快。
I didn't expect you'd be out so soon.
你怎么样？
How are you?
你不平凡的人，先生！ - 观看我的比赛！
You're no ordinary man, sir! - Watch my game!
茉莉，你回家，我会晚一点。
Jasmine, you go home, I'll come later.
我就知道你会这么说。
I knew you'd say that.
看起来像我扰乱你的幸福。
Looks like I've disturbed your happiness.
是谁呢？
Who is it?
不要担心我是谁，来的地方，我会告诉你。
Don't worry about who am I, come to the place I'll tell you.
如果不是茉莉花会死。
If not Jasmine will die.
你立刻来，这是危险的，留在家里。
You come immediately, it's dangerous to stay at home.
危险？
Danger?
你来了，我会告诉。
You come, I'll tell.
快来和与你采取茉莉花。
Come and take Jasmine with you.
茉莉花？ 我应该在哪里来的呢？
Jasmine? Where should I come?
茉莉花，不要留在印度，去马来西亚。
Jasmine, don't stay in India, go to Malaysia.
我所做的一切安排。
I've made all the arrangements.
你想送我走，有一个伟大的时间和她在一起，对不对？
You want to send me away and have a great time with her, right?
这就是你所想的，对不对？
That's what you wish, right?
我要告诉你的好。
I'm telling for your good only.
我会与你同在，送她去马来西亚。
I'll be with you only, send her to Malaysia.
我在谈论你，为什么你拖动到这个Sameera？
I'm talking about you, why are you dragging Sameera into this?
我没有，你叫她自己的。 我不会去任何地方。
I didn't, you called her on your own. I'll not go anywhere.
试着去了解，茉莉花。
Try to understand, Jasmine.
我不想把你的生命处于危险之中，现在会Sameera。
I don't want to put your life in danger, Sameera will come now.
跟她一起去。
Go with her.
你跟我走，向右？ 我会去的。
You told me to go, right? I'll go.
我会去离你不远了。
I'll go far away from you.
我告诉过你多少次不要越过我的路径。
I told you many times not to cross my path.
你觉得你太聪明了吗？
Do you think you're too smart?
血淋淋的，你已经越过剑与迪米特里。
Bloody, you've crossed swords with Dimitri.
我们现在是他的朋友。
We're his friends now.
现在弄明白了吗？
Got it now?
死了！
Die!
没想到这样结束了，对不对？
Didn't expect such an end, right?
嘿，我的生活......
Hey, my life's...
每天每分钟...
every day...every minute...
不只是但凿自己每一刻！
not just that but every moment of it is chiselled by myself!
杀了他！
Kill him!
3Don't让他去。
3Don't let him go.
杀了他！
Kill him!
你已经完成了你的打算！
You've accomplished what you intended!
这仅仅是个开始！
This is just the beginning!
他是一个自我凿成的人...
He's a self chiselled man...
他潦草在命运的额头......
He has scribbled in the forehead of fate...
他放弃了生活中的一切......
He gave up everything in life...
他找遍在痛苦中的幸福...
He searched happiness in pain...
他的恐怖唐...
He's a terror Don...
他是唐笠头，比拉唐...
He's Don of Dons, Billa the Don...
他摇摆唐...
He's a rocking Don...
比拉，唐是愤怒的狮子...
Billa, the Don is rage of lion...
他吊旗火山爆发...
He hoists flag on an erupting volcano...
当他站起来时，人们鼓掌...
When he stand up, people applaud...
他会出现在任何地方...
He'll show up at any place...
他害怕它的知识，没有恐惧......
He scares fear without it's knowledge...